Loot
hua hai
and tell me loot loot lo
in me hi friends welcome to your
investment academy so union budget 0
subscribe today itself do subscribe
behind this here we will talk about
overall 6 points in this video while appointing
subscribe Nirmala Sitharaman
said 2,000 200 see the calendar wide
calendar in my life is the observer
appointed subscribe right now years ago subscribe subscribe
subscribe to the channel in this way this
98100 its focus on infrastructure the
commitment of the Government of India
subscribe and subscribe we consider it a
very important company apple company the
question of appointment is also very less there so I have
tried to comment on that previous segment as well more things will keep on happening in the times to come
and six plus minimum
government and maximum governor's job is to
weigh inauspicious age and if every
business is to do it, it is promoting and supporting many people in this way
now skin subscribe subscribe subscribe doing a great
virtuous deed  If it happens then there could be a problem
there, the
private companies should be properly
monitored, there should be regulators from
there, there should not be any wrong things, there should
not be any manipulation, but if we keep looking at everything with question marks,
then did not hear the right things
and fully any majority
government will do the same, that is what the
minimum maximum governor has paid attention to, so
self-reliance subscribe commitment and
different types of it, some people will be
able to do it properly and some
from the side of direct benefit transfer subscribe
mining sector
question land land reforms
privatization officer given by the obscene subscribe subscribe
subscribe to the channel so
introduction of self-reliant health club 60
subscribe 0 now subscribe here definitely subscribe more
support can come it is not going to
end this is the
responsibility at that time state governments
will dare subscribe there and launch of
Swachh Bharat Mission loot school if
anyone can subscribe
subscribe school  I have
Facebook facility and indirectly
supported the auto sector. It has been possible for commercial
capital cities for around fifteen years.
After that, we can monitor that crop policy.
Dandruff is caused by wwc2. If you want to
subscribe to this channel,
please subscribe. I have put the link on
subscribe manufacturing noble cause.
A prominent one has committed 1.7 lakh rupees.
Subscribe and comment. It is micro, small
and medium enterprises from 240 to 240. The
support that was from this side and
subscribe can be obtained in the school sector. If we
talk about it, then there will be a lot of people
here who are trying to take it
and subscribe.
Secondly, subscribe to Pandey, that means
school. Now subscribe to the school. This
is one of the Kundli State Players on Safety. Bajaj Life Insurance is the second instead of
this region. If this time it is
not possible to subscribe, then
subscribe a little more, then subscribe to
Rs 65 lakh. Big number three, do subscribe to this
commitment from here.
Chanod special edition, more amino acids will
increase the investment and subscribe to a little bit.  I have a
problem, so
please contact other is infrastructure
nice akshar pipeline 1.1 law ministry of
road transport and highways is the most
and the biggest if anyone has transport
ministry please subscribe really really
want to subscribe then subscribe like
subscribe if you have any question
friends actually the rajput who came is
called internal they can never be in any project
subscribe and
subscribe the channel and subscribe the
channel please subscribe and subscribe
multiple will continue for five-ten years
and subscribe with it
half political are logical 50% is very
important to do subscription for long-term
interest rate subscribe and in the coming time
as and when required subscribe
and subscribe to
here debt pension for investment
advisor cities trust vote in adhiraj veerwati can be a
very
good company to subscribe subscribe railway railway
10 subscribe its multiple threats to
employment generation or any other then there are
allied sectors new
job creation can happen there on veer thursday
subscribe develop road transport and
highways definitely subscribe  Subscribe and
subscribe and subscribe the Channel
subscribe in the banking sector,
which buildings are central to a banker
concept, I made a small video about it
on the Marathi channel, so I
said that I am going to cover aloe vera in it, in
which one has to apply for a bad loan,
still they keep on persisting and
because of that there is hatred left, subscribe on that in a
good way, subscribe and subscribe
and subscribe they would
like to convert in the bag where there will be innocent
people, this entry construction company
which buys people and takes care of
how to collect the money or not
and then more than that, that is their
business, but how does the bank feel that if
that entry of ₹100 is there, they have no hope from there,
but man, seriously, the construction
company gives stone super in Dubai, ₹40
best places and the conversation is more,
which is not our benefit, so
Reddy has to pay input tax, but it is good for the bank,
no brother, you were having to do it separately,
that will also be reduced from that,
you have almost turned off the ₹100 and
then  Also some questions if you lost money
net profit up and Akshay increased belly
set for abs and the most important thing there is you
can definitely subscribe
in subscribing which company will get a job or will you start again
then subscribe like subscribe
comment and subscribe
Robin Banks of Operations Kepler Police
Pressure Horn Divya have to give and
subscribe means school appointed subscribe
in the village 22.42 rupees 34.5 subscribe
that mom son were today because everybody was thinking
government concentrate too much on fiscal deficit
or that was not there
so it cannot be much from the rabbit's side
but in the comment the complaint center in
front responsible for all subscribe
point direction tried to take from the
side subscribe so this channel
subscribe also to control diet
chart
Jhajjar all things market from share Sovel
Dhund revision we did so good today so
here see the things of non banking sector share
subscribe from
banking side in 3500 then and subscribe
They can do 522 which includes development of
BPCL, Container Corporation, Shipping
Corporation, Pawanhans, Air India and the
biggest of all. Subscribe and for this reason,
go up to 0.5 inches and subscribe on the skin
and here World Cup 2014
qualification for India through this company.
Denis, if you do it with seniors, then it
definitely looks like India is in a better
position. Decide what game changers can be
seen in this budget, on
which focus is given. Subscribe in UP, which in the
coming time, banks should be
made separate and subscribe to it. The
meeting can be completed very well.
Thanks for the decision of creative people.
Impression of one person companies with no
restrictions of internal. It happens that if
someone wants to start, they get caught in this and
want to complete it. This means how to
create a company private limited,
how long should it be. While doing this, subscribe to this.
Then this is not in the process,
subscribe to the subscribe mission under
video. This means
sector wise beanstalk in school.  Voice also
in the coming time we will see more of these different video
songs, these small video subscribe
recordings, right now
I will take a few questions for you guys, please
subscribe and
open it,
loot morning shooting came hostage who-kun toss with
me opium suggested for development of sexual
harassment pornographic CD and share and
subscribe so do not forget to subscribe to this company
and at the time of subscription do not
forget to subscribe to the company
subscribe so David
Bijnor Bijnor change such boat animals
different as long as there is no account then do
not pay tax, some thought process has been put in I am
not interested in purchasing, there is nothing
from traction point of view, ninth
in Anil Gautam and Vastu effect now
opposite on home finance in PNB housing
loan subsidy in affordable housing, if a
time sensitive one is extended for one more year
then it can have a positive impact,
similarly a lot of benefits have been given at this time due to
duty reduction etc. the
company has done a good business, so in the coming
subscribe finance  The company quantity
subscribes subscribes subscribes
interest rates
are question in subscribing they are in it till then it keeps going so in the
end India is
looking good but IT returns so that's why
that money will come if India
disappoints somewhere then it can go there can be a
train change right now in the short term
so please I don't see that this
train change can be a moment nobody knows so as
long as money subscribes and unlocks
subscribes their house can be
subscribed
good it will happen but it will actually decrease in
12 years subscribe and share subscribe
and subscribe from here subscribe the
channel can be subscribed and
for them subscription has not been given a
little calculation for them you are thinking that you can't do it I will
give you good songs 2019 you well inside also a
mitigation person IT will go now the company has
wastage do subscribe a little bit
on this entire value company subscribes to the channel to a
minimal national investment in
infrastructure depends on
what type of insurance policy you have taken  If there is a
train times cover and premium,
then it comes under section 20mb, it is
less than that, if the cover means you have a page of ₹1000
and your cover is talking on a yearly basis, it has been done
on a premium of ₹1000
and if your cover is below 10,000, then if
Reliance Life
Insurance cover is less than that, then you will be
taxed on it, if it is more than that, then
no tax will be levied, the subscription was done
but the rest has been discussed, so the
fans on whom you have spoken about this weather praise ETC
banking, this
article will the defense budget have any
positive effect and defense staff is not
included in this variation in verses, so
definitely and similarly, a lot of
focus of the Government of India is on Make in
India, its benefits will be available,
we have got a big contender here,
subscribe, Indian companies have
benefits,
yes, gold investment best budget, so that
typing has also fallen today, they have
reduced some duties, due to that a lot of Swadeshi
All the factors that are there can be kept aside,
which were mentioned above, the government should be not
subscribed, then a little etc. Do
n't forget to subscribe to all these things, come to
Gemini, you obscene Ganesh ji, Ravan,
support these robbers, if you think
that the commitments that have been given can be fulfilled,
friends, click on the subscribe button on Thursday, come
to subscribe, don't know at what time I got a message
that brother the video has not been liked, that
live current only, click on the no like button,
quickly here
and Sohan Singh, next question on
loot is the best, it will not make any difference on Sensex and Nifty
index,
both are the same, there is no meaning, there is
more difference, look here, if you want to do a little more constipation
mission, then you cannot say this,
subscribe to,
their views are 167 fans, keeping in mind
and there benefits, temperature has become everywhere,
node node, Thursday, I think it will be less,
if you can see that subscribe, no
problem, set it to less than daily point,
definitely subscribe, 21st
century stock  I am Ajay's subscriber, I am
Ashwani Kumar's remote control, and you want to listen to the
hotel industry, now writing jobs, service, service, service, service, if it is
very low then it does
not subscribe, it is doing a lot, do
not forget to subscribe to the rally in the market, subscribe to
a WhatsApp message, Bureaun, automobile
industry, part of the normal industry, do
two hunting, this industry subscribe,
first continue subscribing for one, two, three months, you will
subscribe to the channel, you will see in the
auto industry, like subscribe
and you should keep it in the future, I will
come to Lucky Lucky Ali, I will say that he had
quoted at his price of 17070, after that it
came above that, we have nothing to do with him,
we had said that see, this is done,
please subscribe button will be there and this
company is subscribing, subscribe, subscribe
for appointed da, pension sector, hot pics, now think, politics, etc., do
not forget to subscribe to our channel and you
can subscribe, subscribe, subscribe,
I have good settings on it, between
funds, Twitter Panchami analyze  Every
temple is used, rotings are given,
so you can subscribe to all these differences by going to
this.in and I don't subscribe, it
is a good budget, subscribe 200,
this subscribe our channel, please
subscribe and subscribe,
this
chatting will also like to extend our
benefits for benefits of bulb school, if you have
not subscribed to this channel then
subscribe quickly friends.